<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.sovietmoviesonline" name="Sovietmoviesonline" version="1.0.1" provider-name="L0RE">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de">Sowjetische und russische Filme mit englischen Untertiteln</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Soviet and Russian movies with English subtitles</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Советские и русские фильмы с английскими субтитрами</summary>
		<description lang="de">In den letzten drei Jahren haben wir die besten sowjetischen und russischen Filme ausgewählt, um sie unseren Zuschauern zur Verfügung zu stellen.[CR]Sie können Filme online ansehen, die eine breite Palette von sehr beliebten Bildern bis hin zu seltenen Funden umfassen.</description>
		<description lang="en">For the last three years we have been selecting the best Soviet and Russian movies in order to make them available for our viewers.[CR]You can watch movies online that span a wide range of very popular images to rare finds.</description>
		<description lang="ru">За последние три года мы отобрали лучшие советские и российские фильмы, чтобы сделать их доступными для наших зрителей.[CR]Вы можете смотреть фильмы онлайн, которые включают широкий спектр очень популярных изображений для редких находок.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Die von diesem Addon dargestellten Inhalte werden von den Erstellern des Addons weder gehostet oder verbreitet, noch stehen die Ersteller in irgendeiner Beziehung zu den Anbietern des Inhalts.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru">Содержимое, отображаемое этим дополнением, не размещается и не распространяется его создателями, равно как и создатели никак не связаны с поставщиками содержимого.</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>https://www.kodinerds.net/index.php/Thread/55451-L0REs-Blog/</forum>
		<website>https://sovietmoviesonline.com</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/kodinerds/repo/tree/master/plugin.video.sovietmoviesonline</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>[B][COLOR orangered]Version 1.0.1  (23.02.2019)[/COLOR][/B] by realvito[CR]
- fixed: Listing of the Categories-Subfolders
- added: Categories = All-Movies, Movies by Decades and Movies by Directors
- added: Switch complete Addon-Language between "EN" and "RU"
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
